One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was a crybaby
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
The word "thank you" has faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
I don't know the answer yet
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
So let's go
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to lose something precious
The voice inside of me
keeps sustaining me
Wicked rain will get in my way
But I won't walk away
So let's go
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to lose something precious
To the future I believe in...
Edward Newgate
You got to be kidding me!
Ace...!
Ace!
Fire Fist Ace is dead!
Straw Hat-boy!
He's losing it!
His life is in danger!
It's Akainu!
I'll get you this time for sure!
Straw Hat!
I'm not gonna let you kill him!
Luffy-kun! Luffy-kun! Stay with me!
Move out of my way!
This war is not over yet!
Take Ace's brother with you, Jinbe!
All right!
Straw Hat's life is how
Ace's life will live on!
Commander... Marco!
We will protect him at any
cost on Ace's behalf!
If we let him die,
it'll be a dishonor to the Whitebeard Pirates!
Luffy-kun, don't lose your sanity!
I told you that I won't
let the brothers get away!
Straw Hat!
Akainu-san!
Pops is furious!
Guys, we gotta get out of here!
Hellhound!
Pops!
Navy HQ is collapsing!
You bastard!
Whitebeard!
Admiral Sakazuki!
– Don't fall!
– Hang on!
Is it over?
Pops!
The plaza has split in two! The
pirates are on the other side!
We are completely separated from Pops!
Pops!
He is still this powerful after his gut has been burnt through?
I'm not done yet.
Everybody, get on the ships!
Pops!
Think about why Pops stayed over there and his last wish for us!
Cry after you get on the ship!
– Pops! Ace!
– Hurry up!
Bring all able ships to the bay!
We won't let you get away!
Hurry up, everyone!
Salome! I can't stop worrying about Luffy!
Hey, look! What is that?!
There is something behind the HQ building!
Oh, they found me!
Not only him! Who are they on the scaffold?
Oh... They noticed us finally.
It's you! How did you all get here?!
Why are they here?!
You bastard.
They're the most heinous criminals
whose existence has been erased
because of their brutality!
He's the biggest of all living things!
The Pirate – "Colossal Battleship" Sanjuan Wolf!
"Colossal Battleship" Sanjuan Wolf
Oh, not only am I found,
but they know who I am!
"Corrupt King" Avalo Pizarro!
"Corrupt King" Avalo Pizarro
I missed being back on the street!
"Heavy Drinker" Vasco Shot!
"Heavy Drinker" Vasco Shot
Am I allowed to kill them all?
"Crescent Moon Hunter" Catarina Devon!
"Crescent Moon Hunter" Catarina Devon
I like you boys, too.
And the Head Jailer of Impel Down...
Shiryuu of the Rain
Shiryuu of the Rain!
They're the Blackbeard Pirates!
Long time no see! I'm glad to be
present at the time of your death!
Pops!
Teach...!
Shiryuu! You...
What happened to Magellan? What happened to Impel Down?!
How did you all get here?!
Doesn't the fact that we are here answer your questions...
Fleet Admiral Sengoku-san?
If you want to know the details...
you can go find out for yourself later.
At any rate, I've decided to team up with these guys.
I bid you farewell.
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
I didn't have a chance to report this to you earlier...
But we received reports that the
Gates of Justice had opened again...
and an unauthorized warship passed through it!
And these people were on that ship?
But there shouldn't be anyone in the control room except our marines...
and nothing out of the ordinary has been reported, either!
How did they get here?
I apologize.
It is quite simple.
Before the Blackbeard Pirates set sail for Impel Down,
I hypnotized the marines in the control room...
and gave them the order that all warships approaching the Gates of Justice...
were to be allowed to pass.
It seems this helped some others as well.
For a pirate, an enemy of the Government...
breaking into Impel Down would've been impossible, since the Gates of Justice would never open.
That's why I increased my reputation and became one of the Seven Warlords!
But I don't need that rank any more!
So your goal was to free those guys?
Indeed! That was my plan all along!
That was all I wanted!
Now do you get it?
None of that matters!
Teach!
Watch out, Captain!
That was really close!
We barely made it out in time.
You aren't holding back!
Well, I guess that's to be expected.
You're the one person I will never call my son, Teach.
You broke the one iron rule on my ship...
You killed a member of the crew!
So that the Fourth Division Commander Thatch may rest in peace...
I will take this fool's life, and settle the score!
Pops!
Marco!
Stay out of this!
Pops!
You got that?!
Let's settle this, Teach!
Fine by me!
What is that black stuff coming out of his body?
Smoke?
Black Hole!
This is the power of the Devil Fruit I stole after killing Thatch!
The mightiest power, the Dark-Dark Fruit!
Have a good taste!
Hey, Pops. Thatch is dead, and so is Ace.
I had always respected and admired you from the bottom of my heart.
But now, you've grown old.
So rusty, you couldn't save a single underling from execution!
Even though I made sure to let Ace live after our battle on Banaro Island.
That bastard...
Now, now... That won't work.
All Devil Fruit abilities are useless against me!
Black Vortex!
Well, Pops? What do you think about my darkness?
It can even suck in Devil Fruit powers, making the users defenseless!
In other words, you can't cause your earthquakes anym—
That hurts...
That hurts, damn it!
Overconfidence... Carelessness...
Those are your biggest weaknesses!
S-Stop it...
Pops, stop it! I'm your son, aren't I?
Are you really going to kill me?!
You did it, Pops!
No... Look at that!
Y-You monster!
You should be dead!
Can't you just die already?!
Pops!
Kill him, you guys!
Do it! Turn him into a honeycomb!
Pops!
You're dying, you say, Roger?
Yeah. I don't have much time left.
Shall I tell you how to get to Raftel, Whitebeard?
Even if you did, I wouldn't go. I'm not interested.
Do you know what the Government calls me these days?
"Gold Roger."
What? Is that your real name?
No, it's not.
My name is Gol D. Roger.
I've met some of those guys
with "D" in their names myself.
There's one in my crew too. His name is Teach.
What's with that "D" anyway?
You want to know?
Alright, I'll tell you.
It's a story from long ago...
I'm out of bullets.
Hey, someone give me another gun!
It's not you...
You're still alive?!
The man Roger is waiting for...
at the very least, Teach...
it's definitely not you.
Just like there are those who carry on Roger's will...
I'm sure someone will appear to carry on Ace's will, someday.
Even if you extinguish his bloodline, there's no way that their flame will ever burn out.
It has been passed down since ancient times...
And in the future... someday...
someone will appear, shouldering the
burden of history for all those centuries,
and challenge the whole world to a fight.
Sengoku...
You and the World Government...
all fear the coming war and the immense impact it will have worldwide.
I don't care myself...
but as soon as someone finds that great treasure...
the entire world will be turned upside down.
And someone will find it.
That day will definitely come sooner or later.
One Piece...
does exist!
Damn you!
Those are some magnificent last words!
Forgive me... my sons...
I'm responsible for one hell of a fool...
But thanks to all of you, I had everything I ever wanted.
This is the end for me.
Now, that's odd! A pirate who doesn't care about treasure?
What do you want, then?
Hey, Newgate!
There's one thing I've wanted, ever since I was a kid.
Oh, there is?
Tell us!
A family.
A family? What's that supposed to mean?
I'm grateful to you.
Farewell, my sons.
H-He died...
while still standing!
Whitebeard is dead.
Even in death, his body did not fall.
His body, striking down foes while riddled with wounds...
was truly monstrous.
The total number of sword wounds he received in this battle...
was 267.
He was shot by 152 bullets.
And was hit by 46 cannonballs.
And despite all this...
his proud back...
over the course of his entire life as a pirate...
never received a single scar from running away!
In memory of Kinryu Arimoto
Editing, Sewil
Quality Control, Pepperjack
Timing, Sewil, Halee
Translation, Yibis, Gaijin
Visual Effects, Datenshi, KaitouYahiko
Graphics, Datenshi
Karaoke, KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking, Halee
Raws, OPFans, FUNi